Guide to the Bob Holman Audio/Video Poetry Collection 1977-2002 MSS 128
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Grassroots Poetry Videos, 1988-2001
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - The New Amazing Grace, 1994 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0485)
    - Ambient Poet: Cari Griffo, 1997 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0486)
    - Lo Maduro de la Cultura, 1994 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0487)
    - Mouthsters 1997 Nat. (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0488)
    - Slam Skit '97, 1997 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0489A)
    - Kennon B. Raines: "Witch Goddess", Undated (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0490)
    - Kennon B. Raines: "Witch Goddess", Undated (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0491)
    - International Drag Poets Ball: "The Year Word Broke", 1996 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0492)
    - Broken Meat, Undated (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0493)
    - Poem in Action: Portarit of Vincent Ferrini, [1990] (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0494)
    - we/eighteen, [1994] (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0495)
    - Elemental: Being There, 1995 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0496)
    - "Messages To The Public'", 1989-1990 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0497)
    - Mike Hazard, Undated (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0498)
    - The Whole Shebang: "Poeting for Etheridge Knight", [1991] (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0499A)
    - Tama Mushi Iro: A Video Of Bug Haiku by Issa, 1996 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0500)
    - Tiger Jack: Mr. Respect, 1998 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0501)
    - The Match That Started My Fire: A film by Cathy Cook, 1991 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0502)
    - [1]-- Border Brujo [2]-- Mi Otro Yo, Undated (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0503)
    - Excerpts From 1001 Real Apes, Undated (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0504)
    - F' loom: Language Music in Live Performance, 1997 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0505)
    - Bob Holman - Digital Master from Carr Session, Undated (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0506)
    - Apropoets, Undated (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0507)
    - Chris Chandler: "Evil", Undated (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0508)
    - Chocolate Kisses, Undated (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0509)
    - End of Lizzie Borden, [1989] (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0510)
    - Battle Sounds Turntablist Festival 1, 1996 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0511)
    - Robert Priest, Undated (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0512)
    - Words Aloud! The Poetry Slam, [1997] (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0513)
    - …elle Senior Project, Undated (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0514)
    - Michael Parker: "Don't Fall Off The Mountain", 1999 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0515)
    - Correspondence: Shalom Gorewitz - 60 Minute Compilation, 1981-1998 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0516)
    - Thai 98 I, [1998] (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0517)
    - Thai 98 II, [1998] (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0518)
    - Jim Northrup: With Reservations, 1995 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0519)
    - Canada's Mid-Riff/ Nite 1, Undated (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0520)
    - Japan, Undated (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0521)
    - Letters Not About Love, 1998 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0522)
- Series VI: Spoken Word History, 1982-2001
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    - "Off the Page: The First Video Poetry Magazine - Vol.1, Issue 1" [Part 1], 1991 (Media ID: 128.1023)
      Duration: [01:07:00]
    - "Off the Page: The First Video Poetry Magazine - Vol.1, Issue 1" [Part 2], 1991 (Media ID: 128.1026)
      Duration: [00:06:00]
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Poetry In Motion: A Film by Ron Mann, [1985] (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0523)
    - Dial-A-Poet Television, Undated (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0524)
    - Azul by Roland Legiardi-Laura, 1990 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0525)
    - Azul, 1986 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0526)
    - [1]-- New York Views [2]-- Gardens, Opera, Rock 'n Roll, [1991] (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0527)
    - Off The Page: The First Video Poetry Magazine - Vol. 1 Issue 1, [1991] (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0528A)
    - The Battle of the Bards: The 9th Annual World Heavyweight Poetry Championship, [1990] (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0529)
    - Great Moments From The Fifth Cowboy Poetry Gathering, 1989 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0530)
    - Baxter Black's 1st Video, 1991 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0531)
    - Moyers: The Power of the Word - #3 & #4, [1989] (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0532)
    - Moyers: The Power of the Word - #1 & #2, [1989] (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0533)
    - Moyers: The Power of the Word - #5 & #6, [1989] (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0534)
    - Moyers: Autry/ Toupe, [1989] (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0535)
    - Voices & Visions 1: Elizabeth Bishop, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0536)
    - Voices & Visions 2: Hart Crane, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0537)
    - Voices & Visions 3: Emily Dickinson, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0538)
    - Voices & Visions 4: T.S. Eliot, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0539)
    - Voices & Visions 6: Langston Hughes, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0540)
    - Voices & Visions 5: Robert Frost, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0541)
    - Voices & Visions 7: Robert Lowell, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0542)
    - Voices & Visions 8: Marianne Moore, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0543)
    - Voices & Visions 9: Sylvia Plath, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0544)
    - Voices & Visions 10: Ezra Pound, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0545)
    - Voices & Visions 11: Wallace Stevens, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0546)
    - Voices & Visions 12: Walt Whitman, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0547)
    - Voices & Visions 13: William Carlos Williams, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0548)
    - Fear and the Muse: The Story of Anna Akhmatova, Undated (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0549A)
    - Michael McClure & Ray Manzarek; "Love Lion", [1991] (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0550)
    - Baxter Black 'Live On Public TV" - In Performance! (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0551)
    - Kovac - Ruff, Undated (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0552)
    - The American Poetry Review Presents Allen Ginsberg, 1988 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0553)
    - Philomene Long's The Beats: An Existential Comedy, Undated (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0554)
    - At The Forks of Troublesome, Undated (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0555)
    - Paris: "The Days of Old", 1992 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0556)
    - Father's Daze: A Film By Mark Pellington, Undated (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0557)
    - Mark Pellington: Public Enemy "Shut 'Em Down", Undated (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0558)
    - Deep Fringe: The Anthology of the 1993 National Poetry Video Festival (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0559)
    - The Poetry Film Sampler, Undated (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0560A)
    - The Sanders Report #16 - Nov 1993 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0561)
    - Teachers & Writers Collaborative: "Determined To See The Far Land", 1990 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0562A)
    - The 17th Annual Poetry/ Film Video Festival Award Winners 1992/ 1993 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0563A)
    - The Language of Life With Bill Moyer: #101 Welcome To The Mainland, 1995 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0564)
    - Ben Harper: Welcome to the Cruel World / Electronic Press Kit, [1993] (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0565)
    - Cittee, Cittee, Cittee: The Poetry of Herschel Silverman, Undated (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0566)
    - William Stafford and Robert Bly: A Literary Friendship, 1992 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0567)
    - Eavan Boland - Lannan Literary Video #42, [1994] (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0568)
    - Imprint - Show 3 - The Spoken Word: "Have You Heard The Word", 1994 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0569)
    - Imprint: "Have You Heard The Word", [1994] (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0570)
    - Todd Colby Variety Pak, [1]--1995 [2]--1993 [3]--1991 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0571)
    - Dana Bryant on MTV Unplugged: "Heat", 1993 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0572)
    - Hal Sirowitz on MTV's Spoken Word Unplugged, 1995 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0573)
    - Hymnody of Earth, Undated (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0574)
    - Sha-key: "Soulsville", Undated (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0575)
    - Elizabeth Murray: Modern Woman, 1995 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0576)
    - Reg E. Gaines: PSA - Mumia, 1996 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0577)
    - McClure/ Hagedorn: Contemporary Voices '96, 1996 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0578)
    - 1996 World Heavyweight Championship Poetry Bout: Troupe, Baca (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0579)
    - 1996 Taos Poetry Circus - Global Voices: Coleman, Allen (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0580)
    - 1997 Taos Poetry Circus - W.H.C.P.B.: Patricai Smith vs. Jimmy Santiago Baca (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0581)
    - 1997 Taos Poetry Circus - Contemporary Voices: Peter Rabbit, Edward Dorn (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0582)
    - American Poetry Literary Project (APL) on ABC News and Good Morning America, 1994 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0583)
    - Murray Lachlan Young: MTV Networks Compilation, Undated (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0584)
    - Murray Lachlan Young: MTV Poet, Undated (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0585)
    - Women of Hope: Latinas Abriendo Camino, [1996] (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0586A)
    - Nike Atheletes, 1997 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0587)
    - Channel 4 Television: "Modern American Poets", Undated (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0588)
    - Off the Page, Undated (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0589)
    - The Best of Spike Jones, Volume Three, 1988 [Clips 1952-1957] (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0590)
    - The Spike Jones Story, 1988 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0591)
    - Lenny Bruce: The Lenny Bruce Performance Film, 1992 [Performance 1965] (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0592)
    - Lenny Bruce without tears: a documentary (of a friend), 1992 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0593)
    - Andy Kaufman: I'm From Hollywood, 1992 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0594)
    - Andy Kaufman: Soundstage, Undated (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0595)
    - Great Russian Writers: Vladimir Mayakovsky, Undated (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0596)
    - The Cask of Amontillado, 1998 (Dub) (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0597)
    - 60 Minutes: Poetry Slam '99, 1999 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0598)
    - ESPN - X Games, Undated (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0599A)
    - Aimé Césaire: Pt. 1 "The Vigilant Island", 1994 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0600)
    - Aimé Césaire: Pt. 2 "Where The Edges of Conquest Meet", 1994 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0601)
    - Aimé Césaire: Pt. 3 "The Strength To Face Tomorrow", 1994 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0602)
    - Poetic Liscence: a short cut, Undated (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0603)
    - God Told Me To, [1997] (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0604)
    - The Best of Ernie Kovacs Vol. 1, [1991] (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0605)
    - The Best of Ernie Kovacs Vol. 2, [1991] (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0606)
    - The Best of Ernie Kovacs Vol. 3, [1991] (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0607)
    - The Best of Ernie Kovacs Vol. 4, [1991] (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0608)
    - The Best of Ernie Kovacs Vol. 5, [1991] (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0609)
    - ESPN - X Games, Undated (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0610A)
    - X Games, Undated (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0611)
    - Andy Kaufman: The Midnight Special, 1981 (Recorded) (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0612)
    - The Best of Spike Jones Volume One, 1985 [Clips 1952-1957] (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0613)
    - The Best of Spike Jones Volume Two, 1987 [Clips 1952-1957] (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0614)
    - The Generous Manas, [1995] (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0615)
    - Poetry In Motion On Television, Undated (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0616)
    - World Heavyweight Championship Poetry Bout: Sherman Alexie vs. Wanda Coleman, 1999 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0617)
    - Andy Kaufman Plays Carnegie Hall, 1979 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0618)
    - World Heavyweight Championship Poetry Bout: Alexie vs. Baca, 1989 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0619)
- Series VII: Spoken Word Video Filmed by Bob Holman, 1991-2002
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Public Poetry, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0620)
      Format: Video 8 mm
    - Public Poetry, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0621)
    - Public Poetry, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0622)
    - Public Poetry, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0623)
    - Public Poetry, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0624)
    - Public Poetry, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0625)
    - All Star Slam! (One Angle), 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0626)
    - All Star Slam! (Hand Held), 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0627)
    - St. Mark's Poetry Project, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0628)
    - Patricia Smith & Wanda Coleman, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0629)
    - 100 Greatest Poets #1, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0630)
    - 100 Greatest Poets #2, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0631)
    - 100 Greatest Poets #3, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0632)
    - First American Sign Language Literary Conference #1, 1991 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0633)
    - First American Sign Language Literary Conference #2, 1991 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0634)
    - First American Sign Language Literary Conference #3, 1991 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0635)
    - First American Sign Language Literary Conference #4, 1991 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0636)
    - First American Sign Language Literary Conference #5, 1991 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0637)
    - [I Allen] 3/6/91, 1991 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0638)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #1, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0639)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #2, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0640)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #3, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0641)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #4, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0642)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #5, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0643)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #6, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0644)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #7, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0645)
    - Alive I, [Early 1990s] (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0646)
    - Alive II, [Early 1990s] (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0647)
    - III Colby/ Holman, [Early 1990s] (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0648)
    - Alive IV, [Early 1990s] (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0649)
    - Ani De Franco / [Nowle Breedlue], Undated (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0650)
    - Stop at Nothing, 1992 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0651)
    - Eritrea I, 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0652)
      Format: MiniDV
    - Eritrea II, 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0653)
    - Eritrea III, 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0654)
    - Eritrea IV, 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0655)
    - Eritrea V, 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0656)
    - Eritrea VI, 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0657)
    - Eritrea VII, 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0658)
    - Eritrea IX, 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0659)
    - Eritrea X, 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0660)
    - Eritrea XI, 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0661)
    - Eritrea XII: Yemen, 2000 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0662)
- Series VIII: Poetry Slams, 1991-1994
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    - SF National Poetry Slam - selects 9/93, 1993 (Media ID: 128.1005)
      Duration: 00:26:00
    - National Slam 1991 #1 (Media ID: 128.1027)
      Duration: 01:24:14
    - National Slam 1991 #2 (Media ID: 128.1028)
      Duration: 01:21:33
    - National Slam 1991 #3 (Media ID: 128.1029)
      Duration: 01:21:43
    - National Slam 1991 #4 (Media ID: 128.1030)
      Duration: 01:54:23
    - National Slam 1991 #5 (Media ID: 128.1031)
      Duration: 01:49:15
    - National Slam 1991 #6 (Media ID: 128.1032)
      Duration: 01:48:12
    - National Slam 1991 #7 (Media ID: 128.1033)
      Duration: 01:37:16
    - National Slam 1991 #8 (Media ID: 128.1034)
      Duration: 00:56:06
    - SF National Poetry Slam, September 1993 (Media ID: 128.1035)
      Duration: 00:33:15
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - National Slam 1991 #1 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0663)
    - National Slam #2 1991 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0664)
    - National Slam #3 1991 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0665)
    - National Slam #4 1991 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0666)
    - National Slam #5 1991 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0667)
    - National Slam #6 1991 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0668)
    - National Slam #7 1991 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0669)
    - National Slam #8 1991 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0670)
    - SF National Poetry Slam - Selects 9/93, 1993 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0671)
    - SF National Poetry Slam 9/93, 1993 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0672)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #1 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0673)
      [Audio Only]
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #2 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0674)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #3 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0675)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #4 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0676)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #5 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0677)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #6 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0678)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #7 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0679)
    - Poetry Slam 10/2/1993 Tape #8 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0680)
    - Poetry Slam Upstairs Room #1, 1993 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0681)
    - Poetry Slam Upstairs Room #2, 1993 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0682)
    - Poetry Slam Upstairs Room #3, 1993 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0683)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 1] (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0684)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 2] (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0685)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 3] (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0686)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 4] (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0687)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 5] (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0688)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 6] (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0689)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 7] (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0690)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/19/94: Tape 8] (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0691)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 1], 1994 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0692)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 2], 1994 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0693)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 3], 1994 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0694)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Backup #3], 1994 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0695)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 4], 1994 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0696)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 5], 1994 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0697)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 6], 1994 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0698)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 7], 1994 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0699)
    - [National Poetry Slam 8/20/94: Tape 8], 1994 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0700)
- Series IX: Metro Home News, ca. 1991
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Interview w/ Bob Holman: Tape #1, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0701)
    - Interview w/ Bob Holman & Miguel Algarin: Tape #2, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0702)
    - Interview w/: Tape #3, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0703)
    - Interview w/ Miguel Algarin & Lois Griffith: Tape #4, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0704)
    - Interview w/ Lois Griffith: Tape #5, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0705)
    - Nuyorican Poet's Café / Metro Home News: Tape #6, 1991 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0706A)
    - Nuyorican Poet's Café - Night / Metro Home News: Tape #10, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0707A)
    - Nuyorican Poet's Café - Night / Metro Home News: Tape #11, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0708A)
    - Nuyorican Poet's Café - Night (Sony) / Metro Home News: Tape #11A, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0709)
    - Nuyorican Poet's Café - Night / Metro Home News: Tape #12, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0710A)
    - Nuyorican / Night - Sony / Metro Home News: Tape #12A, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0711)
    - Nuyorican Café / Night / Metro Home News: Tape #13, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0712)
    - Nuyorican Poets / Night - Sony / Metro Home News: Tape #13A, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0713A)
    - Nuyorican Poet's Café / Night / Metro Home News: Tape #14, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0714)
    - Nuyorican Poet's / Night - Sony / Metro Home News: Tape #14A, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0715A)
    - Stills of Miguel Pinero & Lower Esat Side Tape #1, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0716)
    - Stills of Miguel Pinero & Lower Esat Side Tape #2, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0717)
    - Stills of Miguel Pinero & Lower Esat Side Tape #3, [1991] (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0718)
- Series X: Rise and Shine Productions, 1985-1995
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Unknown to the World, Undated (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0719)
    - Left Over Tears, Undated (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0720)
    - Gold Road to Lonliness, 1993 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0721)
    - Just a Pair OF Eyes Moving, 1994 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0722)
    - Boys & Girls, Undated (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0723)
    - Girls & Boys, Undated (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0724)
    - Outside, Inside Wishes, Undated (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0725)
    - Feels of Dreams, Undated (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0726)
    - Revolving Door, Undated (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0727)
    - Power In Our Hands, 1989 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0728)
    - My Soul Is, 1989 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0729)
    - Change, 1994 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0730)
    - Drugs Are Just A Big Lie, Undated (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0731)
    - Home Poem, 1988 (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0732)
    - The Alien, Undated (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0733)
    - Absence, Undated (Box 30, Media ID: 128.0734)
- Series XI: Miscellaneous Video and Film, ca. 1995-1999
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Urbana, 2000 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0735)
    - "Apollo Comedy Hour"; D. Knowledge's Stand-Up Performance, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0736)
    - Sclactoff Funf, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0737)
    - Millenium Show 2/26/2000 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0738)
    - Gogel Bordello Live 2000 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0739)
    - Passage: Quraysh Ali Lansang, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0740)
    - The Bone Mama..., Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0741)
    - The ABCs of What I Hate, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0742)
    - "City Arts" Show #103: "New York In Verse", 1995 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0743)
    - The Real Deal, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0744)
    - Bob Kaufman @ Vesuvio 3/76, 1976 (Taped) (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0745)
    - Spoken Word I + II, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0746)
    - Planet Carava: Episode 1, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0747)
    - At The Crossroads, 2000 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0748)
    - The People's Poetry Gathering, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0749)
    - The People's Poetry Gathering, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0750)
    - The People's Poetry Gathering, 1999 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0751)
    - The Death of the Old Plymouth Rock Hen (Continuous Loop), 2000 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0752)
    - St. Loius African Chorus, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0753)
    - Fooling With Words Part 1, 2000 (Dub) (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0754)
    - Fooling With Words Part 2, 2000 (Dub) (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0755)
    - Fooling With Words Part 1, 1999 (Dub) (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0756)
    - Fooling With Words Part 2, 1999 (Dub) (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0757)
    - Poem Films by Steve Katz and Nikolai Katz, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0758A)
    - Hunting For Cherubs / DWJ, [1996] (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0759A)
    - USA Poetry, 1994 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0760)
    - D. Di Prima: "Home Turf", 1991 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0761)
    - "Intersection" At The Meeting Point of Music & Poetry - Rough Cut #3, 1996 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0762)
    - Tama Mushi Iro: A Video of Bug Haiku by Issa, 1996 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0763)
    - What He Should Learn From His Dream, 1999 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0764)
    - Memories "96: Buck's Rock Camp, [1996] (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0765)
    - Beccaria Cinema: Senales de Rota, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0766)
    - Robert Bedoya, Bob Holman, Ricci: St. Marks 1/21/1987 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0767)
    - [Dakota's] B-Day April 19, 1986 (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0768)
    - [Unknown], Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0769)
    - Horvaci Torvaki: Knitting Factory & Rehearsal, Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0770)
    - Reggie Gaines: "I Just Want To Catch A Cab!", Undated (Box 31, Media ID: 128.0771)
    - N.Y. Hotline/ [Thouyser]: Korean Mkt. Protest!, [10/30/19??] (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0772)
    - 6356#2, Undated (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0773)
    - The World Heavyweight Championship Poetry Bout 2000: Sherman Alexie vs Bob Holman (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0774)
    - Boys Will Be Boys, 1993 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0775)
    - Saba, Undated (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0776)
    - Carl Watson: "Eddy Paris", Undated (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0777)
    - Jose Padua: NYC Marathon, 1992 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0778)